當我閉上雙眼，
When I close my eyes,
我聽見。
I hear things.
馬車經過時，它的輪子
The sound of a carriage passing
跟鵝卵石路撞出的聲音。
as its wheels wobble against the cobblestone paths.
我淡出於包裹著我的人群的嘈雜聲。
I fade softly against the murmurs of the crowds that encompass me.
風鈴明明被狂風吹著，
Wooden chimes are faintly heard
卻沒人聽的到它的聲音。
against the howling wind.
我聽不清。
Unknown to me.
當我閉上雙眼，
When I close my eyes,
我看見。
I see things.
我看見她，笑著回頭看我，
I see her smiling back at me,
就像我記憶中的那樣，
just like I remembered her doing,
那是多麼遙遠，當時事情還沒這麼複雜。
long ago when things were simpler.
我看見我，在鏡子裡面，
I see myself in the mirror.
晚上作夢時，我知道鏡子裡的是我，
In my dreams, I know it's me,
白天醒著時，我卻是開始懷疑自己。
but in the daylight, I can never be sure.
艷麗的青與赤在天上飛舞，但老實說，再怎麼美麗，
Brilliant blues and pinks cascade across a sky that, to be honest,
我都從沒抬頭看過。
I never look up at.
沒什麼好特別的。
This is nothing profound.
當我閉上雙眼，
When I close my eyes,
我夢見。
I dream of things.
但他們只不過
But they're only familiar
僅只於
to the point
我心中
of a feeling
的感受。
that I know it.
我閉上雙眼，
I close my eyes
在花凋葉落前我都不要醒來。
and dream until every petal falls.
當我閉上雙眼，
When I close my eyes,
我試著忘記張眼時的感覺。
I try to forget what it's like to keep them open.
當我閉上雙眼，
When I close my eyes,
我試著忘記他們的責罵。
I try to forget the blame.
當我閉上雙眼，
When I close my eyes,
我試著記好我的名字。
I try to remember my name.